var questions_Cpp=[{
    "question":"What is data hiding ?",
    "option1":"It is related with hiding internal object details",
    "option2":"It is related with showing internal object details",
    "option3":"It is related with datatypes",
    "option4":"None of above",
    "answer":"1"

},{
    "question":"What is class in c++ ?",
    "option1":"When you define a class, you define a blueprint for a data type.",
    "option2":"When you define a class, you make get more funtionality.",
    "option3":"When you define a class, you define the logic.",
    "option4":"When you define a class, you make debugging.",
    "answer":"1"
},
    {
        "question":"What is object in C++ ?",
        "option1":"Object is part of syntax of a class.",
        "option2":"Object is datatype of a class.",
        "option3":"Object is an instance of a class.",
        "option4":"Object is function of a class.",
        "answer":"3"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is purpose of abstract class ?",
        "option1":"to provide help with database connectivity.",
        "option2":"to provide data input to other classes.",
        "option3":"to provide security to other classes.",
        "option4":"to provide an appropriate base class from which other classes can inherit.",
        "answer":"4"
    },
    {
        "question":"Classes that can be used to instantiate objects are called concrete classes.",
        "option1":"True",
        "option2":"TrueB",
        "option3":"A and B",
        "option4":"None of the above",
        "answer":"1"
    },{
        "question":"What is default visibility mode for members of classes in C++ ?",
        "option1":"Private",
        "option2":"Public",
        "option3":"Protected",
        "option4":"Depends",
        "answer":"1"

    },{
        "question":" What is meant by multiple inheritance?",
        "option1":"Deriving a base class from derived class",
        "option2":"Deriving a derived class from base class",
        "option3":"Deriving a derived class from more than one base class",
        "option4":"None of the mentioned",
        "answer":"3"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following advantages we lose by using multiple inheritance?",
        "option1":"Dynamic binding",
        "option2":"Polymorphism",
        "option3":"Both a & b",
        "option4":"None of the mentione",
        "answer":"3"
    },
    {
        "question":" Which operator is used to create the user-defined streams in c++?",
        "option1":" >>",
        "option2":" <<",
        "option3":"&",
        "option4":" Both >> & <<",
        "answer":"4"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which character is used to terminate the string?",
        "option1":"$",
        "option2":"Null",
        "option3":"Empty",
        "option4":"None of the mentioned",
        "answer":"2"

    }];
